# Hoang Dang Khoa

Address: 8xPlus Apartment, Truong Trinh St, District 12, Ho Chi Minh City

Phone: 01636518543

Email: hoangkhoa9089@gmail.com



#### SUMMARY

More than five years of experience in applications development, testing and troubleshooting.

Strong knowledge of Web-based applications.

Solid understanding of software development life cycles.

Able to teamwork or individual work

The spirit of responsibility, ability to work under pressure and high intensity.

Complete profile: hoangkhoa9089.github.io

### COMPUTER SKILLS

### Languages

- Proficient in: PHP, Java, C#, Visual Basic
- Familiar with: HTML, CSS, Javascript, VBA
- Knowledgeable about: Java Android, IOS Swift and Objective-C

#### Framework

- PHP: Zend 2, Laravel, Slim, Play, Codelgnitor, CakePHP
- Java: Spring MVC, Struts, Hibernate

#### Software

- Database: MS SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle, Postgres, MongoDB
- Platforms: Microsoft Windows 7 and CentOS

# **EXPERIENCE**

## **Labored for Mitani Company**

2017 -Present

AllexceedVietNamInc..

- Develop a large management system for Mitani Company
- Leading a team with six persons
- Technologies: VB.net
- Databases: Oracle

# **Labored for Eyemovic Company**

2017

AllexceedVietNamInc..

- Develop multi kind of website based on requirement of customer
- Install and config server (a LAMP) with custome features, include: cron job, ssh, sync files with rsync
- Leading a team with three persons
- Technologies: Docker, crontab, rsync, PHP, xml-rpc
- Server: Centos 7, Ubuntu 14
- Framework: Codelgnitor
- Databases: MySQL

## Labored for IS-Systems Company

AllexceedVietNamInc..

- Customize the Inventory management system
- Develop based on requirement of different customers
- Develop multi applications for multi devices with different systems, include: Web application, Windows CE, BHT, Android, IOS
- · Leading a team with four persons
- Schedule: Two years
- Technologies: MS Excel, MS Access, VBA, VB.NET, ASP.NET, WCF Web Service, .Net Compact Framework, Windows CE, C++, Java, Android, IOS
- Databases: MS Access, SQL Server, Oracle

Symphonizer 2015

### AllexceedVietNamInc

- This is the system that provides total solutions to industry leading customers of Cable Television businesses for sales and implementation of next generation Integrated Cable Television Operation Management System (Symphonizer) and its integration with other devices and equipment
- Customize features depend on the requirements of customers
- Schedule: Three months
- Technologies: Spring Framework, Struts Framework, Oracle

### Online Shop for Ishida Company

2014

### *AllexceedVietNamInc*

- Build a e-commerce website base on Zend Framework
- Develop frontend and backend with common features of e-commerce website
- Schedule: Four months
- Technologies: Zend Framework, MySQL

## Online Shop Web Service for JTech Company

2013

## All exceed Viet Nam Inc

- Build a Restful API for e-commerce platform base on Play Framework
- Schedule: Two months
- Technologies: Play Framework, Oracle, JSON

## SMS Gateway and Management website

2013

## L.C.S Ltd.

- Delivery solution for SMS messaging with bulk of messages
- Create schedule to sending SMS by website
- Dynamic content of message by multi parameter
- Able to send messages with the Brand Name
- Communicate with NowSMS open source
- Schedule: Nine months
- Technologies: Java, PHP with Codelgnitor, MySQL

## **CIS Management website**

2012

L.C.S Ltd.

- Configuration, administration and reporting of the Asterisk Call Center
- Intuitive interfaces and easy to use
- Schedule: Five months
- Technologies: PHP with Codelgnitor, MySQL, Command line with Linux System, Asterisk API

## Leaning Games for Kids on Android

2011 -2012

Dan Xuan Group

- Perfect for kids and students who need a fun and entertaining educational game to play. This
  bundle of games lets them learn important math, problem solving, and language skills while
  having fun
- Schedule: Six months
- Technologies: Java Android

## **English-Vietnamese Dictionary**

2011 -2012

Dan Xuan Group

- Have a big database with more than 750.000 words and phrases
- · Binary files of database were created based on XML files by indexing and encoding
- Fast search for English definitions, synonyms, word origins, audio pronunciations, example sentences, slang phrases, idioms
- Schedule: Four months
- Technologies: C++, MFC, Thread and Hook

### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Science**

2007 - 2012

HoChiMinh City

• Bachelor Degree of Information Technology